<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentation on Meal Manager</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/</link><description>Recent content in Documentation on Meal Manager</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bazaar Report</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-report/</guid><description>Bazaar Report is a tool to report shopping expenses to the manager. There are two options in Bazaar Report namely Submit New Report and View Previous Report.
Submit New Report
It is mandatory for every member to submit bazaar report after they finish their shopping on assigned date. To do so, tap on Submit New Report to open a dialog box which will ask to input your name; item, quantity, and it&amp;rsquo;s price.</description></item><item><title>Manage Meal</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-meal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-meal/</guid><description>Update MPDPH
Tap on the ellipsis (⋮) menu and select Update MPDPH in order to set the number of meals per day per head and set defaults for Breakfast, Lunch, and Dinner. If any member wants to cancel his meal for a long period of time, then manager will remove the tick mark from Meal is On.
Update Meal
Tap on the hamburger (≡) menu and select Update Meal in order to open a dialog box.</description></item><item><title>Group Message</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/group-message/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/group-message/</guid><description>Group Message is handy for communicating with the manager and other members. Like Bazaar Routine and Bazaar Report, Group Message is also accessible under Discussion menu. Any member can post a message via this option for others to see. Tap on Compose Message, input your name on the box that says Enter Your Name, type your message on the box below and then tap on Send. That&amp;rsquo;s it! Every member will receive your message the next time they open the app.</description></item><item><title>Manage Payments</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-payments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-payments/</guid><description>Update Payment
Tap on the hamburger (≡) menu and select Update Payment to open a dialog box. It will open a list of all member and the amount paid by each member. Input the paid amount in the box labeled with Enter beside the corresponding member (Leave empty if no payment is made) and then tap on Save. You may use the calculator beside the box labeled with Enter for convenience.</description></item><item><title>Announcement</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/announcement/</guid><description>Announcement is a handy feature for a Manager to inform the Members about upcoming changes. Manager can make announcements from Make Announcement option which is accessible from the ellipsis menu. Every member will be notified about the announcement immediately after opening the Meal Manager app next time. Members may view the announcement any time later by tapping on Announcement on the the Home page. Previous announcements can also be viewed by tapping on Announcement followed by See Announcement History.</description></item><item><title>Yet Another Meal Manager App</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/posts/yet-another-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/posts/yet-another-app/</guid><description>There are plenty of apps in Google Play for meal management. We have used them as daily driver for a few weeks. Almost all of the app required to create an account for every member which is inconvenient. Some of them lack basic features like Discussion, Notifications, etc. that we deem essential. In short, none of them satisfied our need.
That is why we launched our own meal management app on Google Play titled Meal Manager - Track Meals on a Shared Flat that is both functional and as simple as possible.</description></item><item><title>Bazaar Routine</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-routine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-routine/</guid><description>Bazaar Routine which is accessible under Discussion menu is a tool for the manager to entitle shopping duties to members. Manager can publish a routine by tapping on Create Routine, filling in the textbox that appears and finally tapping on Publish. Routines are sorted according to date by default.
All members will be able to view the routines created by the manager in Bazaar Routine section.</description></item><item><title>Download and Install</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/getting-started/download-and-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/getting-started/download-and-install/</guid><description>Our Meal Manager app is currently available for free on Google Play. Please click the button below to install it on your device.
Install Meal Manager</description></item><item><title>Log In</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/getting-started/log-in/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/getting-started/log-in/</guid><description>If you have just installed our app, it is time for a new experience. After opening the app for the first time, it will show you Log In screen with the following options:
Are you a Manager?
If you are a manager, choose the Yes button beside the text that says Are you a manager?. It will take you to the next screen where you will be asked to input your Username and Password.</description></item><item><title>Manage Members</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-members/</guid><description>Add Member
Tap on Add Member button at the bottom section of the Home page to open a dialog box. In the dialog box, input Name and tap on Save. You may also input Payment and Meal.
View Member Password
If you are a manager, you can view auto generated password of all members. Just tap on the ellipsis (⋮) menu and select View Member Password. It will open a list of all members and their passwords.</description></item></channel></rss>