<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on Meal Manager</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on Meal Manager</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage Meal</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-meal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-meal/</guid><description>Update MPDPH
Tap on the ellipsis (⋮) menu and select Update MPDPH in order to set the number of meals per day per head and set defaults for Breakfast, Lunch, and Dinner. If any member wants to cancel his meal for a long period of time, then manager will remove the tick mark from Meal is On.
Update Meal
Tap on the hamburger (≡) menu and select Update Meal in order to open a dialog box.</description></item><item><title>Manage Payments</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-payments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-payments/</guid><description>Update Payment
Tap on the hamburger (≡) menu and select Update Payment to open a dialog box. It will open a list of all member and the amount paid by each member. Input the paid amount in the box labeled with Enter beside the corresponding member (Leave empty if no payment is made) and then tap on Save. You may use the calculator beside the box labeled with Enter for convenience.</description></item><item><title>Announcement</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/announcement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/announcement/</guid><description>Announcement is a handy feature for a Manager to inform the Members about upcoming changes. Manager can make announcements from Make Announcement option which is accessible from the ellipsis menu. Every member will be notified about the announcement immediately after opening the Meal Manager app next time. Members may view the announcement any time later by tapping on Announcement on the the Home page. Previous announcements can also be viewed by tapping on Announcement followed by See Announcement History.</description></item><item><title>Manage Members</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/usage/manage-members/</guid><description>Add Member
Tap on Add Member button at the bottom section of the Home page to open a dialog box. In the dialog box, input Name and tap on Save. You may also input Payment and Meal.
View Member Password
If you are a manager, you can view auto generated password of all members. Just tap on the ellipsis (⋮) menu and select View Member Password. It will open a list of all members and their passwords.</description></item></channel></rss>