<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Discussion on Meal Manager</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/</link><description>Recent content in Discussion on Meal Manager</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bazaar Report</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-report/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-report/</guid><description>Bazaar Report is a tool to report shopping expenses to the manager. There are two options in Bazaar Report namely Submit New Report and View Previous Report.
Submit New Report
It is mandatory for every member to submit bazaar report after they finish their shopping on assigned date. To do so, tap on Submit New Report to open a dialog box which will ask to input your name; item, quantity, and it&amp;rsquo;s price.</description></item><item><title>Group Message</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/group-message/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/group-message/</guid><description>Group Message is handy for communicating with the manager and other members. Like Bazaar Routine and Bazaar Report, Group Message is also accessible under Discussion menu. Any member can post a message via this option for others to see. Tap on Compose Message, input your name on the box that says Enter Your Name, type your message on the box below and then tap on Send. That&amp;rsquo;s it! Every member will receive your message the next time they open the app.</description></item><item><title>Bazaar Routine</title><link>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-routine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Byte-Saga.github.io/mealman-doc/discussion/bazaar-routine/</guid><description>Bazaar Routine which is accessible under Discussion menu is a tool for the manager to entitle shopping duties to members. Manager can publish a routine by tapping on Create Routine, filling in the textbox that appears and finally tapping on Publish. Routines are sorted according to date by default.
All members will be able to view the routines created by the manager in Bazaar Routine section.</description></item></channel></rss>